

CONTACT INFO



patriciarcamp@gmail.com



612-750-8882



linkedin.com/in/patcamp



github.com/pataseya

TECHNOLOGIES

- Ruby Ruby on Rails
- HTML CSS Bootstrap
- Ruby Gems APIS
- SQL Active Record
- Git GitHub -Heroku
- Unix line command
- WordPress Wix
- Raiser's Edge, e-Tapestry
- Object-Oriented Programming

IMPACT

Wrote winning nominations for AFP Central Ohio National Philanthropy Day Awards 2014, 2015 and 2016

2015 Member of 3rd place winning Team at Startup Weekend

2015 Fundraising event generated \$57,000 with sold out attendance

2013 Secured \$30,000 for a collaborative grant to upgrade a playground

2011 Ohio Public Images Award for fundraising event

2011 Employee of the year

PAT CAMP

DEVELOPER – PROJECT MANAGER

I've expanded my technical competencies to include web app development using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Ruby and Ruby on Rails. I have a keen interest in pairing these new skills with my experience in marketing, communications and project management with a new position or project.

I'm a natural organizer and problem solver. I get the big picture and can drill down to the details. Equally comfortable in customer forward-facing roles or working independently, I am confident I can contribute to your business objectives in meaningful ways.

EXPERIENCE

2013 - 2018 Campwell Communications, Owner Columbus, OH

BIG KITTY LABS - GRANT WRITER, CONTENT DEVELOPMENT & PROJECT MANAGEMENT

Worked on several mobile app projects with several clients

THE BREATHING ASSOCIATION - MARKETING & COMMUNICATIONS

Developed annual communications plan, wrote and published monthly print and e-newsletters, maintained website content and social media posts and managed events.

THE FURNITURE BANK OF CENTRAL OHIO - MARKETING & DEVELOPMENT Developed annual communications plan, impact reports, marketing collateral and donor communications. Managed marketing events and migration to new website.

2008 - 2013 Association for the Developmentally Disabled Worthington, OH

DIRECTOR OF MARKETING & DEVELOPMENT

EXECUTIVE ASSISTANT & ADMINISTRATIVE SERVICES MANAGER

Established and managed inaugural fundraising events, wrote grants and increased donor base by 1500% in four years. Developed operations and employee manuals, branding standards and annual reports. Produced marketing and training videos, initiated social media and e-marketing channels and maintained website content. Negotiated and coordinated installation of a multi-site phone system, and designed and implemented a corporate contract management system and a records retention system. Developed and instructed new employee orientations.

2007 - 2008 MillerCoors

Milwaukee, WI

SENIOR ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT

Provided executive-level support for two finance vice presidents assigned to the marketing division.

PAT CAMP

EDUCATION

Tech Talent South Code Immersion 2018 Spring Cohort

B.S., Computer Science Fisher College of Business The Ohio State University

COURSEWORK

Association of Fundraising Professionals (AFP) Fundamentals of Fundraising

John Glenn College of Public Affairs Management Advancement for the Public Service (MAPS) Classes

Social Role Valorization Training

EXPERIENCE (CONTINUED)

2004 - 2007 Alzheimer's Association Minnesota-North

Dakota Minneapolis, MN

EXECUTIVE ASSISTANT AND BOARD LIAISON

Developed board management protocols, wrote bylaws, board and employee manuals while providing administrative support to the executive director and development director.

1983 - 1989 E.I. DuPont de Nemours Company, Inc.

Wilmington, Delaware

Systems and Marketing Analyst - Systems Supervisor - Sr Systems Analyst Programmer Analyst - College Relations Representative

Programming, systems analysis and regression testing. Campus recruitment and relocation. Design, implementation and training of an expert system for use by the sales force. Supervised systems development and support team for a manufacturing plant site.

COMMUNITY INVOLVEMENT

2018	Kids Code Teacher - Tech Talent South
2013 - present	Elder Care Manager for parents
2010 - present	Webmaster & Executive Committee The University Women's Club at OSU
2014 - present	Pool Committee Secretary Sycamore Hills Resident Association
2012 - 2016	Membership Materials AFP of Central Ohio
2007 - 2008	Life Teen Facilitator St. Martin of Tours Catholic Church
1997 - 2003	Catechist and Faith Formation Coordinator Pax Christi Catholic Community
1998 - 2003	Art Masterpiece Volunteer Coordinator Cedar Ridge Elementary School
1994 - 1998	President and Historian The Mother's Connection, Early Childhood PTA
1991 - 1992	Elementary School Volunteer